https://bestcutgems.com/store-policies/

Tahitian Cultured Pearls
What is a Cultured Pearl?
What is a Pearl?
The Ultra Tec V5 Upgrade Review
Who Facets Gemstones?
Zultanite Tidbits
Much More Here!!
Tahitian Cultured Pearls
What is a Cultured Pearl?
What is a Pearl?
The Ultra Tec V5 Upgrade Review
Who Facets Gemstones?
Zultanite Tidbits
Much More Here!!
Store Policies
United States and Puerto Rico Policies:Please scroll down for Canada and all other International Policies
SHOP WITH CONFIDENCE!It is very important that you understand and read our policies carefully to avoid confusion when ordering. Our policies are in place to protect our customers and ensure the best customer service.If you have any questions regarding the policies outlined on this website, please contact our customer service department at:Best Cut GemsP. O. Box 640279Beverly Hills, FL  34464-0279Phone: 269.303.4414E-mail: info@bestcutgems.comPAYMENTAt Best Cut Gems we offer a secure site and easy payment with Mastercard, Visa, American Express, Discover, Apple Pay, Paypal credit and our BCG Layaway Plan.  You can also pay via Paypal even if you don't have a Paypal account. You can pay with credit card or via your checking account through Paypal.  It is quick and easy!Please note all transactions over $10.000.00 must be paid by direct bank wire transfer. Email us for further instructions on how to do this, very simple.SHIPPINGPlease provide a complete address for delivery during business hours. Orders will be shipped within 2-3 business days, unless otherwise stated. If shipping is delayed for any reason, we will notify you as soon as possible.We use insured USPS Mail and UPS/FedEx shipping.  No express deliveries on Saturday or Sunday.REFUND POLICYThere will be a 15% restocking/consultation fee for all returned or cancelled orders.This is to cover the cost of the Credit Card and Paypal fees that I still have to pay because of the transaction.  I only have had one cancelled order that a gentleman made on an engagement ring that I refunded to him minus the shipping cost. (The engagement had been called off, it was a pitiful story)  The next month I received my bank statement and was hit $43.00 for that transaction fee, even though I refunded the money.BCG Layaways Refunds will only be issued a merchandise credit, no exceptions!Refunds for the cost of an item are made if the purchaser is dissatisfied and notifies Best Cut Gems within 2 (two) days and returns the item within 5 (five) days of receipt of the item. No Exceptions!  Requests for refunds must be made by phone or e-mail.  Best Cut Gems will issue a refund upon receipt of the item(s) if the item is in an unaltered and undamaged state, less any shipping and handling charges. Shipping and Handling costs are not refundable.Please note: Any returned items sent to me after the 5 (five) day return period, you will be issued a merchandise credit. This means you will have a credit of the amount the returned item was (example, $25.00 gemstone = $25.00 merchandise credit) and you may use it towards another gemstone or any jewelry item, any merchandise that I have listed on the Best Cut Gems website.Send merchandise via insured shipment.  This will protect you in case the package is damaged or lost in transit.Send Returned Items To:  BCG                                          5231 W. Chippewa Drive                                          Beverly Hills, FL   34465 Please note that the customer is responsible for the cost of shipping items to Best Cut Gems and for return shipping charges!THERE ARE NO REFUNDS ON SPECIAL CUSTOM ORDERS!TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS POLICYBest Cut Gems is not responsible for typographical errors.CUSTOMER PRIVACY POLICYBest Cut Gems will not give, sell, or rent your personally identifiable information, including e-mail, personal data, and credit card information, to anyone.For more information regarding privacy, please contact info@bestcutgems.comSECURITY POLICYIn our effort to ensure a safe and secure online shopping experience, we wish to share information about our exhaustive user information protection and transaction security policies.a) SSL Encryption:At any instance when a customer enters personal data while shopping or checking out of our site, we process the information via secure software technology to guarantee the safest shopping environment. When the customer is ready to check out from our site after making a purchase, a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) connection is invoked to transfer all sensitive data in a safe and secure way.The SSL encrypts the information, including name, address, and credit card number, so that unauthorized individuals cannot observe, decode, or misuse it as it is transmitted over the Internet.
Canadian Policies:Please scroll down for all other International countries!
SHOP WITH CONFIDENCE!It is very important that you understand and read our policies carefully to avoid confusion when ordering. Our policies are in place to protect our customers and ensure the best customer service.If you have any questions regarding the policies outlined on this website, please contact our customer service department at:Best Cut GemsP O Box 640242Beverly Hills, FL  34464Phone: 269.303.4414E-mail: info@bestcutgems.comPAYMENTAt Best Cut Gems we offer a secure site and easy payment with Mastercard, Visa, Discover, Apple Pay, Paypal credit and our BCG Layaway Plan.  You can also pay via Paypal even if you don't have a Paypal account.  You can pay with credit card or via your checking account through Paypal.   It is quick and easy!   If you have problems processing your order through our website, it is due to our tight security on credit cards.  In that event please use the PayPal option for your method of payment, as we are using them for our International Order Processing!If you prefer you can pay by a direct wire transfer.  Email linda@bestcutgems for further instructions to do a wire transfer, very easy.Canadian Buyers are responsible for all Duties and Taxes!SHIPPING If you mark your purchase as a "GIFT" I cannot mark GIFT on the Custom Declaration form.  This is a violation of federal and international laws.  All customs declarations will be filled out completely and truthfully. Depending on your country and postal service you may be responsible for additional customs, tax or VAT fee's. Please be aware of your carriers policy before purchasing. Best Cut Gems is not responsible for any additional fee's.  You, the customer will be responsible for all custom, duties, taxes, handling charges and VAT fees in your country. NO refunds on International orders.  International Custom Forms: I must fill out a customs form to ship into your country. The contents information and cost is automatically filled in when I generate the label. International Orders: 1-5 weeks for delivery If your country is not listed please email me. Need your purchase expedited?  Please email me.Please provide a complete address for delivery during business hours. Orders will be shipped within 2-3 business days, unless otherwise stated. If shipping is delayed for any reason, we will notify you as soon as possible.We use insured First Class USPS Mail International, Express Mail International and FedEx for shipping.   You have an option of the 3 different shipping rates when you place your order.To save you money on shipping charges, the larger jewelry items will be shipped in silk pouches instead of the larger, heavier, gift boxes.All shipments will be made to credit card billing address only.REFUND POLICYNo refunds on Canadian Orders!TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS POLICYBest Cut Gems is not responsible for typographical errors.CUSTOMER PRIVACY POLICYBest Cut Gems will not give, sell, or rent your personally identifiable information, including e-mail, personal data, and credit card information, to anyone.For more information regarding privacy, please contact info@bestcutgems.comSECURITY POLICYIn our effort to ensure a safe and secure online shopping experience, we wish to share information about our exhaustive user information protection and transaction security policies.a) SSL Encryption:At any instance when a customer enters personal data while shopping or checking out of our site, we process the information via secure software technology to guarantee the safest shopping environment. When the customer is ready to check out from our site after making a purchase, a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) connection is invoked to transfer all sensitive data in a safe and secure way.The SSL encrypts the information, including name, address, and credit card number, so that unauthorized individuals cannot observe, decode, or misuse it as it is transmitted over the Internet.
International Policies for all other Countries
SHOP WITH CONFIDENCE!It is very important that you understand and read our policies carefully to avoid confusion when ordering. Our policies are in place to protect our customers and ensure the best customer service.If you have any questions regarding the policies outlined on this website, please contact our customer service department at:Best Cut GemsP O Box 640279Beverly Hills, FL   34464Phone: 269.303.4414E-mail: info@bestcutgems.comPAYMENTAt Best Cut Gems we offer a secure site and easy payment with Mastercard, Visa, Discover, Apple Pay, Paypal credit and our BCG Layaway Plan.  You can also pay via Paypal even if you don't have a Paypal account.  You can pay with credit card or via your checking account through Paypal.   It is quick and easy!   If you have problems processing your order through our website, it is due to our tight security on credit cards.  In that event please use the PayPal option for your method of payment, as we are using them for our International Order Processing!If you prefer you can pay by a direct wire transfer.  Email linda@bestcutgems for further instructions to do a wire transfer, very easy.The BCG Layaway Plan can also be used for International BuyersInternational Buyers are responsible for all Duties and Taxes!SHIPPINGIf you don't see your country listed on the order form and we may be able to make special arrangements for you!Please provide a complete address for delivery during business hours. Orders will usually be shipped within 2-3 business days, unless otherwise stated. If shipping is delayed for any reason, we will notify you as soon as possible.The BCG Layaway Plan can also be used for International Buyers If you mark your purchase as a "GIFT" I cannot mark GIFT on the Custom Declaration form.  This is a violation of federal and international laws.  All customs declarations will be filled out completely and truthfully. Depending on your country and postal service you may be responsible for additional customs, tax or VAT fee's. Please be aware of your carriers policy before purchasing.  Best Cut Gems is not responsible for any additional fee's.  You, the customer will be responsible for all custom, duties, taxes, handling charges and VAT fees in your country. NO refunds on International orders! International Custom Forms: I must fill out a customs form to ship into your country. The contents information and cost is automatically filled in when I generate the label. International Orders: 1-5 weeks for delivery If your country is not listed please email me. Need your purchase expedited?  Please email me. Please provide a complete address for delivery during business hours. Orders will be shipped within 2-3 business days, unless otherwise stated. If shipping is delayed for any reason, we will notify you as soon as possible.We use insured First Class USPS Mail International and Express Mail International. We also use FedEx for Express shipping.  You have an option of the 3 different shipping rates when you place your order.To save you money on shipping charges, the larger jewelry items will be shipped in silk pouches instead of the larger, heavier, gift boxes!REFUND POLICYNO REFUNDS ON INTERNATIONAL ORDERS! TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS POLICYBest Cut Gems is not responsible for typographical errors.CUSTOMER PRIVACY POLICYBest Cut Gems will not give, sell, or rent your personally identifiable information, including e-mail, personal data, and credit card information, to anyone.For more information regarding privacy, please contact info@bestcutgems.comSECURITY POLICYIn our effort to ensure a safe and secure online shopping experience, we wish to share information about our exhaustive user information protection and transaction security policies.a) SSL Encryption:At any instance when a customer enters personal data while shopping or checking out of our site, we process the information via secure software technology to guarantee the safest shopping environment. When the customer is ready to check out from our site after making a purchase, a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) connection is invoked to transfer all sensitive data in a safe and secure way.The SSL encrypts the information, including name, address, and credit card number, so that unauthorized individuals cannot observe, decode, or misuse it as it is transmitted over the Internet.
×
OK
Join our newsletter
Email Address
